{"data":[{"question":"Emily and Tracy ___ catch the first train but couldn't.","a":"tried to","b":"managed to","c":"could","d":"were able to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Try: to attempt to do or get something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"One mad behavior is not enough to ___ a man is mad.","a":"decide","b":"prove","c":"explain","d":"judge","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Prove: to show that something is true by providing facts, information","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"When did the speech begin? \"When all the attendants ___, the candidate began his speech.\"","a":"sit","b":"seated","c":"seat","d":"were seated","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Seat: to arrange for someone to sit somewhere\n- Simple past tense (same tense with verb \"began\") + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"People usually ___ late to celebrate the New Year.","a":"come up","b":"keep up","c":"sit down","d":"stay up","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Stay up: to not go to bed at the time you would normally go to bed","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The bus stopped and ___ the crowd of passengers.","a":"picked up","b":"got on","c":"got up","d":"lifted up","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Pick up: lift something\/somebody up","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The fire had been ___ 5 minutes before the firefighters arrived.","a":"put away","b":"put out","c":"put down","d":"put off","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Put out: to make a fire etc stop burning","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Where is your passport? \"My passport was ___.\"","a":"lost","b":"robbed","c":"stolen","d":"not here no more","answer":"3","explain":"\n - Steal: to take something that belongs to someone else","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"It will ___ one good to have some outdoor activities.","a":"be","b":"make","c":"feel","d":"do","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Do one good: Be of benefit to one","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The whole class ___ a lot of time on this math problem.","a":"cost","b":"spent","c":"took","d":"paid","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Spend: to use time doing a particular thing or pass time in a particular place","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The principal ___ to all of the teachers how to solve this issue.","a":"said","b":"told","c":"explained","d":"informed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Explain: to tell someone about something in a way that is clear or easy to understand","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}